I received this notice that she is
withdrawing from the academy.
Why didn't you stop her?!
Enrolled students hold the right to
receive instruction to become a hero.
They are also at full liberty
to relinquish that right.
It is not my duty to stop those
who choose to leave the academy.
How can you be so heartless?!
Every child must one day
leave their parents' nest.
I do consider myself an adult, you see.
I wouldn't be so uncouth as to stop her.
Your Majesty!
I'm not done here yet! Also...
Calm down a bit.
Take a good look at him.
Huh?
Your Majesty.
We'll make sure we bring Sophie back.
Oh?
And do you know where she's headed?
She'll be looking for her five sisters.
According to my investigation,
it looks like they go between
a number of different bases.
Should we start looking
at the most likely ones?
Okay!
Let's get going, then.
Not so fast!
Have you thought about
why she went by herself?
Well...
Sophie didn't want any of
you to sully your hands.
What?
The only way to stop those five...
is to kill them.
That can't be!
There must be some other
way to convince them...
Those girls will stop at nothing.
Sophie went alone precisely
because she realized that.
The world is more than what
we see in the light of day,
and she knows that she existed
in the shadows to begin with.
That's why she wants to put an
end to this with her own hands.
So her friends will not dirty theirs.
You all need to think long and
hard about this until dawn.
Episode 12
The Sophie Series (Part 2)
Parent!
Master, you are going to
search for Sophie?
Yeah.
I'll go, too!
Sophie is my friend!
I shall be by your side,
wherever you go, Master.
Just the three of us, huh?
Hm? I'm going, too.
Did Maria agree to this as well?
That crybaby said that she
can't abandon a friend.
I see.
So that makes five of us.
Shall we get going, Great Hero?
I'm not the Great Hero anymore.
Blade, you're late!
See, didn't I tell you?
I figured Blade was just waiting
around the dorm entrance.
What, Blade?
Couldn't make up your mind?
How sluggish for a superorganism.
It only took me five minutes to decide!
My bad for being so late!
Okay, let's go!
Sophie!
Eliza, I found her.
That's a relief.
I'll send everyone your way.
Please!
Stop running away!
Please, let's talk about this.
I have a request as well.
Please let me be.
Sophie.
We all understand how you feel,
and what you're trying to do.
So there's no need to worry...
You've got it wrong.
What?
There's something I haven't told you.
I am a human who was created for
the Artificial Great Hero Project.
Artificial... Great Hero?
During the war, research was conducted
to try and artificially produce a human
with powers equal or greater
to the Great Hero's.
I was the twelfth test subject.
Everyone who took part in the
research was supposedly arrested,
but I hear that some samples and
research data have been stolen.
Those five girls are the samples in question.
Someone continued the research,
incubating them and giving them commands.
The reason they exist...
is to surpass the Great Hero.
The Great Hero...
You mean the one and only?
But if that's the case,
why are they after Blade's life?
Well...
Oh, I get it!
They want to test their capabilities
on this superorganism!
If they can't even defeat a superorganism,
they stand no chance against
the Great Hero himself.
That must be it.
U-Um...
Yeah, sure, that's gotta be it.
They can be quite dense, huh?
I've caused you all so much
trouble by getting you involved.
That's not true...
My past has finally caught up with me.
I wondered all along whether it was okay
to have so much fun... to be so happy.
Was it okay for a human impostor like me
to live happily as a real person?
That's why I'm going back
to where I used to be.
I'll protect all of you.
Even if it costs me my life.
It may not have been for long,
but being able to walk out in the sun...
made me happy.
Ow.
Ow... that hurts.
How ridiculous.
If walking in the sun makes you happy,
then keep doing it.
I mean, I also used to...
have eyes like this,
and I never looked like I was
happy or having fun, right?
That's true.
Huh?!
But look, thanks to Blade,
I was able to change.
You turned into a bit too
much of a lost cause, though.
Besides, if killing them is the
only solution, then we'll also...
No, we won't do that.
What?
But His Majesty said...
I know what the king said,
but killing them isn't the answer.
It's impossible.
Thanks to their neural programming,
their creator's orders are absolute.
Is there nothing we can do?
Even if there were...
Because of all the harsh
modifications they've undergone,
they don't have much longer to live.
How awful...
You have a plan, right?
Nope, not at all.
What?!
Still, I want to do something.
I want to save Sophie's sisters.
Sisters...
Which is why I want all of you to help.
Sophie, are you okay with that?
Sophie.
Give your life to me.
What?!
Okay.
That was fast! Are you sure?!
I mean... that's... He just....
What are you getting
worked up about, Earnest?
I-I get it!
You want to be friends
with those girls, right?
Okay, let's do it.
So, do you have any good ideas?
You're leaving it all to me?!
Well, sure, I don't mind.
I've come up with a plan.
Let me know when you can't move anymore.
I'll dispose of you.
Huh?!
You know I'm still good to go!
I'll crush you!
I still wanna destroy more!
Destroy! Destroy!
Yes, very good.
The only reason you exist is
to transcend the Great Hero.
Kill the Great Hero.
Kill, kill, kill.
Une.
I found this outside.
A letter of challenge.
It must be a trap.
We'll put an end to this.
Do you really think they'll
answer that challenge?
It's fine.
I know I would go for sure.
I-I see...
Sniff, sniff...
I smell the same scent as Sophie!
They have arrived.
I've been waiting.
We'll kill you.
That is what we exist to do.
I see.
I was hoping I could be
friends with all of you.
You understand the plan, right?
You will be the only one fighting.
If we attack as a group,
they're sure to run away.
However, with only one target,
they should continue to fight,
even knowing that it's a trap.
Blade...
I know the plan,
but not being able to help...
Listen up!
The goal is not to defeat them,
but to deplete their energy.
C'mon, die!
Adamantine Body!
Please endure all of their attacks.
Destroy! Destroy!
Easy for you to say!
I know the superorganism can pull it off!
If you manage to deplete their energy...
Be on constant lookout,
and don't break the blockade!
There must be someone
giving orders to the five of them.
Make sure you capture them.
Now this is a realistic exercise!
No, it's the real deal!
We'll arrest the person who created them.
Then, we'll make them tell us the
parameters to reprogram and save them!
So... please don't die!
Hi-yah!
Hey, teach me again.
How to kill you!
Oh, no!
Blade!
Have faith in Blade.
I know!
I know that...
But still!
He can still use moves like that?
Not being able to do anything...
Other than sit and watch...
Anna.
There's still something
we can do, isn't there?
Artificial Great Hero Power.
Deadly Earth Crash!
What?! The ground...
Be crushed by the planet, and die!
Three! Two! One!
I'll send you to heaven.
Artificial Great Hero Power!
Are they all real?
Blade!
Take this!
Dragon Smash!
Too bad.
This is the end.
Artificial Great Hero Power.
I'll wipe you out, jackass!
Blade!
This is the Super God Technique,
Absolutely Unbreakable Barrier.
Ugh, that sure is a name.
So this is it...
Ah...
No way!
Earnest, hand that over!
Huh? But your sword...
Believe in me!
Okay!
Destroy! Destroy! Destroy! Destroy!
Ah!
I've got this.
Artificial Great Hero Power.
Blade.
Take control of this power.
It should be easier for the
real Great Hero, right?
Are you sure?
It'll be pretty painful.
My life belongs to you.
Use it all you want.
Artificial Great Hero Power!
Great Hero Power!
You did well, Sophie.
Blade...
Take this.
Um, what was that move called again?
Well, whatever works, I guess.
Earnest Monster Beam!
Hey! Don't give it a weird name!
What's wrong?
Not gonna finish me off?
My time is up.
Time?
What does that mean?
Huh?
H-Hey!
By time, you don't mean...
Snap out of it!
Hey!
Our lifespan... measured in days...
is fourteen days.
Until... sunset today.
How beautiful...
Eliza!
You heard her, right?!
There's no time left!
We're out of time!
I just finished looking over
the research data from
the modification facility
where they were born.
What atrocious workmanship.
I'd say they were lucky to
last fourteen whole days...
Blade...
It's not working!
I can't heal them!
The powers of the Great Hero and
Demon King defy the laws of physics.
They disrupt the laws of cause and effect.
Claire's powers work by decreasing entropy.
They won't work when
causality has been severed.
Isn't there some way to save them?!
That's right!
There's the person who made
Une and the others, right?!
If we ask them...
It's no use.
We did find their creator.
However...
He's dead!
And not within the last fourteen days!
Long before that...
By the time they were born,
he was already dead!
The truth is... that there
never were any commands...
Can't you do something with
that science of yours?
I could do research.
With my intellect, I might be able
to find a way to reprogram them.
But there's not enough time.
Science has its limits as well.
It can't solve everything
in the snap of your fingers!
Damn it all!
If only I was more of a genius!
Blade.
Bring all of them... my sisters, here.
Une.
Wake up.
You still haven't used your
Artificial Great Hero Power.
You will all die,
but there's a way for you to keep living.
I failed to carry out my orders.
What point is there in living?
You can surpass me.
Keep on living, and try to surpass me.
If you can, that is.
Hmm, that sounds pretty fun.
There's no way...
But the chances aren't zero.
I might win if it was a different activity.
Destroy, destroy...
Une.
I understand.
Artificial Great Hero Power.
Blade.
Take control of her power.
So that their souls...
their minds... enter me.
Okay.
Leave it to me.
Um... are you Une?
That's right.
What's wrong?
I just came to see if
you were feeling better.
When you are, I'll be the one to kill you.
Don't forget it.
Yeah.
That's what you all say.
What about the others?
They say they want to talk to you.
But before that...
Sophie?
Yes.
It looks like my sisters let me take control.
Sounds like you have it rough.
Is everything okay?
Well...
It feels like having six children.
Six?
Isn't that one too many?
The sunny disposition that
brings a smile to your face
As well as the heroic sense of justice
They may be a part of me,
but that's not all there is
That image of me
Has taken on a life of its own
Hey, wait up
Won't you be friends with me?
Let's shake hands, another self of mine
The wounds we cannot bear alone
The dangers that we keep hidden
We're all hiding them within
Standing ready to strike
The shadow lurking beneath the light
The muffled sounds coming from my lips
They make me feel that I am alive
It's a sign
Ah, it's hopeless!
It's my turn!
Now this is a true realistic exercise!
Gil.
About the magical beast brought here today...
I received word that there's been a mix-up.
It seems they delivered a different
beast than the one you ordered.
I thought it was a little too powerful.
Looks like I'm going to be busy.
Knock 'em dead!
Final Ep!! Good Work!!
Blargh...
Hi-yah-yah-yah!
Hi-yah-yah-yah...
Hey, Asmodeus!
You can do better than that!
No more...
I'm really done for...
My lord!
Let us fight in tandem!
Why me?!
Please, everyone.
I've got this.
Dragon Smash!
Hi-yah!
Like this.
Destroy!
Artificial Great Hero Power!
How many does that make?
I'll land the final blow—
Bow before me!
According to my high-spec calculations...
No effect.
It really doesn't look good.
Oh, there's no need to worry.
After all, he's the Great Hero!
Hmm?
What's wrong, everyone?
Mmm! This tonkatsu curry's so good!
You lousy...
Superorganism!